Guide to the Naegele Outdoor Advertising records, 1978-2002 and undated RL.11324
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Naegele Poster Designs, 1981-1993 and undated; 1
  - S. Garrity RE/Max, undated (Box 46)
  - Shell Island, undated; 2 folders (Box 46)
  - Sheraton, 1985-1990; 2 folders (Box 46)
  - Shoe Shak/Legends, undated; 2 folders (Box 47)
  - Shoney's, undated (Box 47)
  - Showbiz Pizza Place, undated (Box 47)
  - Silver Fox/Hallmark Square, 1981 (Box 87)
  - Smash! Video, 1991 and undated; 3 folders (Box 47)
  - Smithfield's Chicken 'N Bar-B-Q, 1991-1992 and undated; 3 folders (Box 47)
  - Sound Ace Hardware, undated (Box 47)
  - Sound Furniture and Appliances/Sealy, 1990-1991; 2 folders (Box 47)
  - Southern Water Conditioning, 1987 (Box 48)
  - Speedy Burgers, undated (Box 48)
  - Spinnaker Point, undated (Box 48)
  - The Spirit of Kitty Hawk, undated (Box 48)
  - Sporting goods, 1986 (Box 48)
  - Sportsman's Lodge, undated (Box 83)
  - Stalcup Living Room Gallery, undated (Box 48)
  - Steak-Out, undated; 3 folders (Box 48)
  - Steak-Out, 1991 (Box 83)
  - Sterling Edition, undated; 2 folders (Box 49)
  - Steve's Calabash Seafood, undated (Box 49)
  - St. James Plantation, undated; 3 folders (Box 49)
  - Subway, 1989-1991 and undated; 7 folders (Box 49)
  - Sub-Stational Deli and Sub Shop, undated (Box 49)
  - Suggs and Harrelson/Carolina Beach Realty, undated; 2 folders (Box 49)
  - Summer Winds, undated (Box 83)
  - Sun-Drop beverage, undated (Box 50)
  - Support Art Education PSA, 1988 and undated; 2 folders (Box 50)
  - Surf 107, 1991 and undated; 5 folders (Box 50)
  - Surf City, undated; 2 folders (Box 50)
  - Suzuki, undated (Box 50)
  - Suzuki, Stevenson, undated (Box 50)
  - Swansboro, undated (Box 50)
  - Swansboro United Methodist Church, undated (Box 50)
  - Sweetwater swimwear, undated (Box 50)
  - Talking Threads Clothing, undated (Box 51)
  - "Talk With Your Kids" PSA, undated (Box 51)
  - Tallberg Chevrolet, undated (Box 51)
  - Tapestry Theater, 1989-1990 and undated; 2 folders (Box 51)
  - Teleco Business Phones, 1987-1991; 2 folders (Box 51)
  - That's Amore, 1987-1988 and undated; 4 folders (Box 51)
  - Thornton Chiropractic, undated (Box 51)
  - Tideline Marine, 1990; 2 folders (Box 52)
  - The Tides, undated (Box 52)
  - Tinga Nursery, 1987-1988 (Box 52)
  - Tireville, undated; 6 folders (Box 52)
  - Tireville, undated; 7 folders (Box 53)
  - Tobie's Lounge, undated (Box 53)
  - Tobie's Lounge, 1990 (Box 83)
  - Tom Fazio, undated (Box 53)
  - Tony's Foreign Car Center, undated (Box 53)
  - Trade Winds Apartments, undated (Box 53)
  - Travel Agents International, 1986 (Box 54)
  - Trave-L-Lodge, undated (Box 54)
  - Turner Tolson Furnishings, 1988-1989; 5 folders (Box 54)
  - Turner Tolson Furnishings, undated; 4 folders (Box 55)
  - Twin Wood, undated; 2 folders (Box 83)
  - United (real estate), undated; 2 folders (Box 55)
  - United Negro College Fund, undated (Box 55)
  - United Resorts, 1991 (Box 55)
  - United States Coast Guard, undated (Box 55)
  - United States Marine Band, 1986 and undated; 2 folders (Box 55)
  - United States Navy Band, 1987 (Box 55)
  - United States of America PSA, 1990 (Box 55)
  - United States Olympic Festival, 1987 (Box 83)
  - United States Olympics, 1987 (Box 55)
  - United Way, 1991 (Box 55)
  - University Motors, undated (Box 55)
  - University Motors, 1984-1986; 2 folders (Box 83)
  - University of North Carolina--Wilmington, 1990-1991; 2 folders (Box 55)
  - University of North Carolina--Wilmington, 1991 and undated; 2 folders (Box 56)
  - USPA and IRA, 1989 (Box 56)
  - USS North Carolina battleship, 1981 (Box 56)
  - Val-Pak, 1987 and undated; 2 folders (Box 56)
  - Various images/designs, undated; 2 folders (Box 56)
  - Various images/designs, undated (Box 57)
  - Victoria Place, 1989 (Box 57)
  - Village Flea Mall, undated; 2 folders (Box 57)
  - Village Green Christmas Shop, undated (Box 57)
  - The Villager Gift Shop, 1991 (Box 57)
  - Vision Cable, undated; 2 folders (Box 57)
  - Visual Improvement Onslow, 1986 (Box 57)
  - Volvo, 1985 (Box 57)
  - WAAV AM 980, undated; 3 folders (Box 57)
  - Wachovia, undated; 2 folders (Box 57)
  - Waterfront Condos, undated (Box 58)
  - Watson Builders, undated (Box 58)
  - "We Do" political, undated (Box 58)
  - WECT, undated; 3 folders (Box 58)
  - Wells Oldsmobile/Quality Ford/Rick Edwards Buick, 1992 and undated; 3 folders (Box 58)
  - Western Steer Family Steakhouse, undated (Box 58)
  - Westminster Homes, undated; 2 folders (Box 58)
  - WGNI 103, undated; 2 folders (Box 58)
  - Whizz Mart, undated (Box 58)
  - "Who Cares" political, undated; 2 folders (Box 58)
  - Wicker Works, undated; 3 folders (Box 59)
  - Wildflower development, undated (Box 59)
  - Willetts Real Estate, 1986-1987 and undated; 6 folders (Box 59)
  - Wilmington Athletic Club, 1987 and undated; 2 folders (Box 59)
  - Wilmington Downtown, undated (Box 60)
  - Wilmington Has It All PSA, 1987 (Box 83)
  - Wilmington Market Place, 1986 and undated; 2 folders (Box 60)
  - Wilmington Symphony, undated (Box 60)
  - Wilson County Tourism, undated (Box 60)
  - Wilsons, undated (Box 60)
  - Winn Dixie/CoGo, 1991 (Box 60)
  - Winter Park School, undated (Box 60)
  - "Wish We Could Vote" PSA, 1985 (Box 60)
  - Wizard of Oz, undated (Box 60)
  - WJKA-TV26, 1985 and undated; 4 folders (Box 60)
  - WLAS AM910, undated (Box 83)
  - The Women's Exporium, 1988 (Box 60)
  - Woodlake Country Club, undated (Box 60)
  - Woofer 'N Tweeter/Panasonic, undated; 2 folders (Box 61)
  - Word of Faith ministry, 1988; 2 folders (Box 61)
  - WQSM 98.1 FM, 1991 (Box 61)
  - WRCM 92.1 FM, undated; 2 folders (Box 61)
  - Wrightsville Beach, 1985 (Box 61)
  - Wrightsville Green, 1988 and undated; 2 folders (Box 61)
  - Wrightsville Marina Yacht Club, undated (Box 61)
  - WRNS, undated (Box 62)
  - WWAY, undated (Box 62)
  - WXOR 105 FM, undated (Box 62)
  - Yahweh Center, 1988 and undated; 2 folders (Box 62)
  - Yard Work/Greg Bullock, undated (Box 62)
  - Yellow Rose Saloon, 1988 (Box 62)
  - Yogurt and Cream, undated (Box 62)
  - Z103 FM, undated (Box 62)
  - Zike's Fitness Center, undated (Box 62)
- Fairway Poster Designs, 1991-2002 and undated; 2
  - A-Rent All--Chris Best, 1999 (Box 63)
  - Addy Awards, 1992 (Box 86)
  - Addy Awards, 1992 (Box 87)
  - Affordable Dentures--Ralph Braswell, 1999 (Box 63)
  - AllTel--Angela Cooper, 2001; 2 folders (Box 63)
  - American Eagle--Kirk Edgerton, 1999 (Box 63)
  - Amoco, Dairy Queen--Barbara Matthews, 2000 (Box 84)
  - Amoco, White Swan BBQ, 1998 (Box 84)
  - Applebee's--Bryan Stevenson, 1998 (Box 63)
  - Applebee's--Linda Beam, 2000 (Box 63)
  - Arnold's Diner--Ralph Braswell, 2001 (Box 63)
  - Artsplosure--Don Pierce, 1999-2002; 4 folders (Box 63)
  - Artsplosure, 2002 (Box 63)
  - Atrium Furniture--Chris Best, 2000 (Box 63)
  - Azalea Festival, 1994 (Box 87)
  - Bayonet Golf--Kirk Edgerton, 1998 (Box 63)
  - Beacon Hill--Kirk Edgerton, 1999 (Box 63)
  - Beezer Homes, Country Club Heights--Kirk Edgerton, 2001 (Box 84)
  - Berkeley Mall--Barbara Matthews, 2000 (Box 63)
  - Berkeley Mall--Bryan Stevenson, 1999 (Box 63)
  - Best Western--Bryan Stevenson, 1996-1999; 2 folders (Box 63)
  - Biscuit Kitchen--Rebecca Jackson, 1999 (Box 63)
  - Boardwalk RV Park--Angela Cooper, 1998 (Box 63)
  - Boat Show Raleigh Civic Center, 1993 (Box 63)
  - Bob King Automall, 1992 (Box 63)
  - Bob Evans--Bob Watson, 2002 (Box 63)
  - Bob's Auto--Angela Cooper, 2000 (Box 63)
  - Bobby Hardee Landscaping--Marty Scarborough, 2001 (Box 63)
  - Bogue Inlet Pier, 1993 (Box 63)
  - Bogue Inlet Pier--Angela Cooper, 2000 (Box 63)
  - Bojangles'--Ralph Braswell, 1999 (Box 63)
  - Bojangles'--Marty Scarborough, 2002 (Box 63)
  - Bostrom Ford--Chris Best, 2001 (Box 63)
  - Boys and Girls Clubs of Pitt County, 1991 (Box 63)
  - Boys Club--Angela Cooper, 2001 (Box 63)
  - Brent Adams and Associates--Rebecca Jackson, 1999 (Box 63)
  - Britt and Britt Attorneys--Mike Russell, 1999 (Box 63)
  - Bud Light, 1996 (Box 63)
  - Capital Bank--Chris Best, 1999-2000; 2 folders (Box 64)
  - C&S Paint--Angela Cooper, 1999 (Box 84)
  - Capital Ford Service--Chris Best, 1999-2000; 2 folders (Box 64)
  - Cardinal Motors, 1993 (Box 64)
  - Carolina Classic Golf--Don Pierce, 2000 (Box 64)
  - Carolina Home Medical--Bryan Stevenson, 1999 (Box 64)
  - Carolina Home Medical--Barbara Matthews, 2000 (Box 64)
  - Carolina Hurricanes--Chris Best, 2000; 2 folders (Box 64)
  - Carolina Mobile Home--Tod Allen, 2000 (Box 64)
  - Carolina Mobile Home--Kirk Edgerton, 1999 (Box 64)
  - Carolina Steakman--Mike Russell, 1999 (Box 64)
  - Carraba's--Kirk Edgerton, 1999-2001; 2 folders (Box 64)
  - Castle Bay Golf Course--Mike Russell, 2000 (Box 64)
  - Century 21--Barbara Matthews, 2000 (Box 64)
  - Century 21--Angela Cooper, 2000 (Box 64)
  - Cherry Oil Amoco-King's--Barbara Matthews, 1999 (Box 64)
  - Chevron--Phillip Goodwin, 2001 (Box 64)
  - Chik Fil-A--Ralph Braswell, 1999-2000; 2 folders (Box 64)
  - Chik Fil-A--Ralph Braswell, 2000 (Box 64)
  - China Buffet--Mike Russell, 2001 (Box 64)
  - China Garden--Barbara Matthews, 2001 (Box 64)
  - Christian Outreach--Chris Best, 2000 (Box 64)
  - City Junction--Angela Cooper, 2000 (Box 64)
  - City of Wilson--Linda Beam, 1999 (Box 64)
  - Cloth Barn--Barbara Matthews, 2000 (Box 64)
  - Coastal Carolina auto dealer--Angela Cooper, 2001 (Box 64)
  - College Foundation, 2000 (Box 64)
  - College Foundation--Thomas Steger, 2001 (Box 64)
  - Colony Homes--Kirk Edgerton, 2001 (Box 64)
  - Comfort Inn--Jim Leake, 2001 (Box 64)
  - Comfort Inn Garner--Chris Best, 2000 (Box 64)
  - Comfort Inn--Kirk Edgerton, 2001 (Box 64)
  - Comfort Inn Washington--Bryan Stevenson, 1999 (Box 64)
  - Comfort Inn Wilmington--Mike Russell, 1999 (Box 64)
  - Comfort Suites--Chris Best, 2000; 2 folders (Box 64)
  - Conn Trucking--Tod Allen, 2000 (Box 65)
  - Conoway Lodging/Motel 6--Rebecca Jackson, 2000 (Box 65)
  - Courtyard Durham--Chris Best, 1999 (Box 65)
  - Cracker Barrel--Kirk Edgerton, 1999-2000; 5 folders (Box 65)
  - Cracker Barrel--Rebecca Jackson, 1999 (Box 65)
  - Crawford-Norwood Realty--Tod Allen, 1999 (Box 65)
  - Crocker's Marine--Mike Russell, 1992 (Box 65)
  - Cumberland County Library--Rebecca Jackson, 2001 (Box 65)
  - Cypress Island--Mike Russell, 1999 (Box 65)
  - Days Inn, 1992 (Box 65)
  - Days Inn--Ralph Braswell, 2002 (Box 65)
  - Deacon Jones--Barbara Matthews, 2001 (Box 65)
  - Denny's--Kirk Edgerton, 2000 (Box 65)
  - Domino's/Nintendo, undated (Box 65)
  - Down East Travel--Rebecca Jackson, 2000 (Box 65)
  - Dufus and Younce Attorneys--Rebecca Jackson, 1999 (Box 65)
  - Duplin General Hospital, 1992 (Box 65)
  - Dynasty Homes--Kirk Edgerton, 1999-2001; 3 folders (Box 65)
  - Eastern Petroleum/Shell/Exxon/Dairy Queen--Linda Beam, 1999 (Box 65)
  - Eastern United Tire--Bryan Stevenson, 1998 (Box 65)
  - Edgecombe Social Services--Thomas Steger, 2000 (Box 65)
  - Eve Lights, 1991 (Box 86)
  - Evening With Friends--Don Pierce, 1999 (Box 65)
  - Express Inn--Kirk Edgerton, 2001 (Box 66)
  - Exxon--Linda Beam, 1999 (Box 66)
  - Exxon/McDonald's--Linda Beam, 1999 (Box 66)
  - Fairfield Inn--Angela Cooper, 2000-2002; 6 folders (Box 66)
  - Family Funeral Care--Kirk Edgerton, 1999 (Box 66)
  - Fashions for the Working Woman--Angela Cooper, 1999 (Box 66)
  - Fast Freddy's--Angela Cooper, 2001 (Box 66)
  - First American Savings Bank, 1992 (Box 86)
  - First Baptist Church--Rebecca Jackson, 1998 (Box 66)
  - First Citizens Bank--Ralph Braswell, 2000; 2 folders (Box 66)
  - First Citizens Bank, undated; 2 folders (Box 84)
  - First Citizens Bank, undated (Box 86)
  - First Night--Don Pierce, 1999-2001; 3 folders (Box 66)
  - First South Bank--Linda Beam, 2000 (Box 66)
  - Fortis Homes, Crockett's Ridge--Chris Best, 1999 (Box 66)
  - Fox Trail Mini Self Storage--Barbara Matthews, 2001 (Box 66)
  - Fran's Beachwear--Angela Cooper, 1999 (Box 66)
  - Frederick's flooring, 1992 (Box 66)
  - Freeman Motors--Mike Russell, 1999 (Box 66)
  - Freeman Motors--Mike Russell, 2000 (Box 67)
  - Fuddrucker's--Angela Cooper, 1999-2000; 2 folders (Box 67)
  - Fuller's BBQ--Mike Russell, 1999 (Box 67)
  - Furniture Fair/Flooring America--Angela Cooper, 1999-2000; 2 folders (Box 67)
  - God Poster religious--Barbara Matthews, 2000-2001 (Box 67)
  - In God We Trust PSA--Barbara Matthews, 2001 (Box 67)
  - Golden Retriever Rescue--Joy, 2002 (Box 67)
  - Golden Sands--Mike Russell, 2000 (Box 67)
  - Golfin' Dolphin--Angela Cooper, 1999 (Box 67)
  - Good Hope Hospital Urgent Care--Kirk Edgerton, 1999 (Box 67)
  - Grace Church--Barbara Matthews, 1999-2001; 3 folders (Box 67)
  - Greenville Toyota--Bryan Stevenson, 1998 (Box 67)
  - Greenville Toyota--Jim Leake, 2002 (Box 67)
  - Habitat for Humanity--Vance S., 2002 (Box 67)
  - Hampton Inn Fayetteville--Kirk Edgerton, 1999 (Box 68)
  - Hampton Inn Garner--Kirk Edgerton, 1999 (Box 68)
  - Hampton Inn Goldsboro--Bryan Stevenson, 1999 (Box 68)
  - Hampton Inn Greenville--Bryan Stevenson, 1999 (Box 68)
  - Hampton Inn New Bern--Angela Cooper, 2000 (Box 68)
  - Hampton Inn Safari Grille--Chris Best, 1999 (Box 68)
  - Hampton Inn Wilson--Barbara Matthews, 2001 (Box 68)
  - Handy Andy--Kirk Edgerton, 2001 (Box 68)
  - Hardee's--Mike Russell, 1996-1998; 2 folders (Box 68)
  - Hardee's/Citgo--Marty Scarborough, 2001 (Box 68)
  - Hastings Ford, 1997 (Box 84)
  - Hill's--Barbara Matthews, 2001 (Box 68)
  - Hill's Pharmacy--Bryan Stevenson, 1999 (Box 68)
  - Hill's Pharmacy--Barbara Matthews, 2000 (Box 68)
  - Hilton/Morgan's Sports Bar--Chris Best, 2000 (Box 68)
  - Hiro Restaurant--Mike Russell, 1999 (Box 68)
  - Holiday Inn Express--Chris Best, 1999 (Box 68)
  - Holiday Inn Express--Linda Beam, 1999 (Box 68)
  - Holiday Inn Express Dunn--Kirk Edgerton, 2001 (Box 68)
  - Holiday Inn Express Goldsboro--Barbara Matthews, 2001 (Box 68)
  - Holiday Inn Express Hillsborough--Kirk Edgerton, 1999 (Box 68)
  - Holland Landscaping--Angela Cooper, 1999 (Box 68)
  - Home Max--Kirk Edgerton, 1999 (Box 68)
  - Home Sod--Rebecca Jackson, 2001 (Box 68)
  - Hooper and Thurston--Linda Beam, 2000 (Box 68)
  - Hot Wax Surf Shop--Mike Russell, 2000-2001; 2 folders (Box 68)
  - Hot 96.3 FM--Angela Cooper, 1999 (Box 68)
  - Hurricanes--Chris Best, 2000 (Box 68)
  - Independence Mall, 1991 (Box 69)
  - Innkeeper--Chris Best, 2000 (Box 69)
  - Infant of Prague--Angela Cooper, 1999 (Box 69)
  - Interpreters on the Phone--Marty Scarborough, 2001 (Box 69)
  - Jacksonville NC--Angela Cooper, 2001 (Box 69)
  - Jameson Inn--Chris Best, 1999-2001; 2 folders (Box 69)
  - Jimmy V 2000--Don Pierce (Box 69)
  - J.L. Powell and Co.--Phillip Goodwin, 2001 (Box 69)
  - Joe Alcoke Auto Center, 1992-1993; 2 folders (Box 69)
  - Johnson Drug Company, 1991 (Box 69)
  - Josh Allen--Bryan Stevenson, 1999 (Box 69)
  - Josh Allen--Barbara Matthews, 2001 (Box 69)
  - JR--Linda Beam, 1999 (Box 69)
  - JR--Barbara Matthews, 2000 (Box 69)
  - JR Brassieres--Linda Beam, 2000 (Box 69)
  - JR Cut Rate, 2002 (Box 69)
  - JR Dutch Master, 2002 (Box 69)
  - JR La Corona Cigars, 2002 (Box 69)
  - JR Perfume, 2002 (Box 69)
  - JR Stetson--Ralph Braswell, 2000 (Box 69)
  - JR Towels, 2002 (Box 69)
  - Jubilee Amusement Park, 1995 (Box 69)
  - Junior League of Raleigh--Don Pierce, 2001 (Box 70)
  - Ken Sutton State Farm Insurance--Rebecca Jackson, 2001; 3 folders (Box 70)
  - Kentucky Fried Chicken--Phillip Goodwin, 2001 (Box 70)
  - Kingdom Homes--Bryan Stevenson, 1999 (Box 70)
  - Kings Grant--Rebecca Jackson, 2000 (Box 70)
  - Kings Grant--Tod Allen, 2002 (Box 70)
  - Kmart, Winn Dixie, undated (Box 86)
  - KOA Campgrounds--Phillip Goodwin, 2001 (Box 70)
  - Kosterman Chiropractic--Rebecca Jackson, 1999 (Box 70)
  - Landing @ Southport--Mike Russell, 1999 (Box 70)
  - Lee County Chrysler--Chris Best, 2000 (Box 70)
  - Lenoir College--Barbara Matthews, 1999 (Box 70)
  - Lodge America--Chris Best, 1999 (Box 70)
  - Lodge America--Chris Best, 2001 (Box 86)
  - Lone Star Steakhouse, 1992 (Box 84)
  - Lone Star Steakhouse, 1992 (Box 86)
  - Mai Tai--Angela Cooper, 2001 (Box 70)
  - Marine Chevrolet, 1991 (Box 70)
  - Massey Toyota--Barbara Matthews, 2000 (Box 70)
  - Massey Toyota--Rob House, 2002 (Box 70)
  - Mattress Depot--Angela Cooper, 1999 (Box 70)
  - McCall's Bar-B-Que and Seafood--Rob House, 2002 (Box 70)
  - McDonald's--Mike Russell, 1999 (Box 70)
  - McDonald's--Angela Cooper, 2000-2001; 2 folders (Box 70)
  - McDonald's Beltline--Chris Best, 2000 (Box 70)
  - MegCor Discount Golf--Mike Russell, 1997 and undated; 2 folders (Box 70)
  - Miller, 1991 (Box 70)
  - Monster's Pizza--Angela Cooper, 2000 (Box 70)
  - Motel 6, 1998 (Box 84)
  - Murray Memorial Baptist Church, 1992-1993; 2 folders (Box 71)
  - Nahunta Pork Center--Linda Beam, 1999 (Box 71)
  - National Dodge, undated (Box 71)
  - The Nature Basket--John Altman, 2002 (Box 71)
  - North Carolina Department of Agriculture--Mike Russell, 1999 (Box 71)
  - North Carolina Symphony, 1991 (Box 71)
  - Northwest Creek Marina, undated (Box 86)
  - Oakwood Homes--Kirk Edgerton, 2000 (Box 71)
  - Oakwood Homes--Linda Beam, 1999 (Box 71)
  - Ocean Ridge Hurricane Repair--Mike Russell, 1999 (Box 71)
  - Oh! Brian's--Linda Beam, 1999 (Box 71)
  - Outback--Angela Cooper, 1999 (Box 71)
  - Owens Furniture--Rebecca Jackson, 2002 (Box 71)
  - Osprey Waterfront Living, undated (Box 71)
  - Pap's Grill--Angela Cooper, 2001 (Box 71)
  - Papa John's--Angela Cooper, 2001 (Box 71)
  - Parker Lincoln--Don Pierce, 2000 (Box 71)
  - Pawn Plus--Tod Allen, 2002 (Box 72)
  - Pets +--Mike Russell, 1997-1999 (Box 72)
  - Piggly Wiggly--Ralph Braswell, 2002 (Box 72)
  - Quality Inn and Suites--Barbara Matthews, 2001 (Box 72)
  - Quincy's Family Steakhouse--Mike Russell, 1999-2000; 2 folders (Box 72)
  - R&A Sausage--Barbara Matthews, 2000 (Box 72)
  - Raleigh Community Hospital--Chris Best, 1999; 2 folders (Box 72)
  - Raleigh-Durham International Airport, undated (Box 72)
  - Red Roof--Chris Best, 2000-2002; 2 folders (Box 72)
  - Redden Honda--Chris Best, 2001 (Box 72)
  - Regency Housing--Don Pierce, 2000 (Box 72)
  - Reliance Transmissions--Tod Allen, 2000 (Box 72)
  - Residence Inn--Chris Best, 2000 (Box 72)
  - Rhudy's--Rebecca Jackson, 2001 (Box 72)
  - Rightway--Barbara Matthews, 2001 (Box 72)
  - Risen Homes--Mike Russell, 1999 (Box 72)
  - Riverbirch Corner Shopping Center--Chris Best, 1999 (Box 72)
  - Rock Creek Golf Club, 1999 (Box 72)
  - Rocky Mount All American City--Linda Beam, 1999 (Box 72)
  - Rocky Mount Fair--Brenda Reaves, 2001 (Box 72)
  - Rogers Bay--Angela Cooper, 1999 (Box 73)
  - Rucker John's--Angela Cooper, 2001 (Box 73)
  - Safety Board, 2000-2002; 2 folders (Box 73)
  - Sale Automall--Bryan Stevenson, 1999 (Box 73)
  - Sale Automall--Barbara Matthews, 2000 (Box 73)
  - Sale Automall--Rob House, 2002 (Box 73)
  - Sam's Mobile Home Sales--Mike Russell, 2001 (Box 84)
  - Sand Jam--Angela Cooper, 2000 (Box 73)
  - Sander's Ford--Angela Cooper, 1999-2001; 3 folders (Box 73)
  - Sanford Antique Mall--Chris Best, 2000 (Box 73)
  - Schilsky-McLaughlin Chiropractic--Angela Cooper, 2000 (Box 73)
  - Scudder and Hendrick--Marty Scarborough, 2001 (Box 73)
  - Secure Care Self Storage--Rebecca Jackson, 2002 (Box 73)
  - Shelton's Harley-Davidson--Barbara Matthews, 2001 (Box 73)
  - Shoney's--Ralph Braswell, 1999 (Box 73)
  - Shoney's--Mike Russell, 1999 (Box 73)
  - Shoney's--Angela Cooper, 1999-2000; 2 folders (Box 73)
  - Shoney's--Chris Best, 2001-2002; 2 folders (Box 73)
  - Smash!, 1991 (Box 73)
  - South of the Border--Linda Beam, 1998 (Box 73)
  - Spell's Mechanical Services/Bryant Heating and Cooling, undated (Box 73)
  - Spiritual Advisor--Brenda Reaves, 2001 (Box 84)
  - Steak 'N Hoagie--Kirk Edgerton, 2000 (Box 74)
  - Steak-Out, undated (Box 74)
  - Stephenson's--Marty Scarborough, 2001 (Box 74)
  - Stereo World/USA Tires--Rebecca Jackson, 1999 (Box 74)
  - Storage USA--Rebecca Jackson, 2001 (Box 74)
  - Suburban Lodge--Rebecca Jackson, 2000 (Box 74)
  - Subway--Mike Russell, 2000 (Box 74)
  - Super 8 Motel--Kirk Edgerton, 1999 (Box 74)
  - Super 8 Motel--Linda Beam, 2000 (Box 74)
  - Super 8 Motel, 2001 (Box 74)
  - Super 8 Motel--Thomas Steger, 2001 (Box 74)
  - Super 8 Motel--Angela Cooper, 2001 (Box 74)
  - Talbert Building Supply--Chris Best, 2001 (Box 74)
  - Tanner and Romary--Marty Scarborough, 2001 (Box 74)
  - Tarheel Geo, 1992 (Box 74)
  - Tarheel Oldsmobile, 1992 (Box 74)
  - Tireville, 1992-1993; 2 folders (Box 74)
  - Tireville, 1992 (Box 75)
  - Torrey Homes--Chris Best, 2001 (Box 75)
  - Travelodge--Thomas Steger, 2000 (Box 75)
  - Travel World/Hardee's/Shell--Kirk Edgerton, 2000 (Box 75)
  - Triangle Waffle, 1992 and undated; 2 folders (Box 75)
  - United Carolina Bank, undated (Box 84)
  - Universal Studios--Linda Beam, 1999-2000; 2 folders (Box 75)
  - University Health Systems of Eastern Carolina--Bryan Stevenson, 1999 (Box 86)
  - University of North Carolina Hospital--Chris Best, 2001 (Box 75)
  - Uzzle Motors--Kirk Edgerton, 2000; 2 folders (Box 75)
  - Victoria Homes--Angela Cooper, 1999 (Box 75)
  - Village Vineyards--Thomas Steger, 2001 (Box 75)
  - Volaris--Angela Cooper, 2001 (Box 75)
  - Wachovia, 1991 (Box 75)
  - Wayne Community College--Barbara Matthews, 2000 (Box 75)
  - WellPath--Chris Best, undated (Box 75)
  - Wells Auto--Mike Russell, 1999 (Box 75)
  - Wendy's--Rebecca Jackson, 1999 (Box 75)
  - Wendy's--Linda Beam, 1999 (Box 75)
  - Wendy's, 2001 (Box 75)
  - White Oak Crossing, 1999 (Box 76)
  - White Oak Crossing--Angela Cooper, 2000 (Box 76)
  - White's Tire--Chris Best, 2000 (Box 76)
  - Whitley Jenkins and Riddle LLP--Barbara Matthews, 1999 (Box 76)
  - Wine and Cheese Emporium--Rob House, 2002 (Box 76)
  - WKIX--Kirk Edgerton, 1999 (Box 76)
  - WLGX Smooth Jazz 106.9 FM, 1999 (Box 84)
  - Woodlake--Rebecca Jackson, 1999 (Box 76)
  - Worthy Is the Lamb--Angela Cooper, 1996-2000 (Box 76)
  - Your Way Housing Center, undated (Box 76)
- Naegele Slides, 1982-1990 and undated; 3
  - 87 presentation, 1987 (Box 88)
  - 87 sales presentation, Jim Pridgen, Wilmington, 1987 (Box 88)
  - 96.3/Harvey's, undated (Box 88)
  - Advertising, undated (Box 88)
  - Alcohol, undated; 2 folders (Box 88)
  - Auto dealerships, undated (Box 88)
  - "Bananas" presentation, undated (Box 88)
  - Beaches and boating, undated (Box 88)
  - The Cape, undated (Box 88)
  - Cigarettes and smoking, undated; 2 folders (Box 88)
  - Clothing, undated (Box 88)
  - Creative contest, 1982-1985; 3 folders (Box 88)
  - Dancing, undated (Box 88)
  - Designs, undated (Box 88)
  - Education, undated (Box 88)
  - Electronics, undated (Box 88)
  - Entertainment, recreation, travel, undated (Box 88)
  - Financial, undated (Box 88)
  - Food, undated; 2 folders (Box 88)
  - Food, undated (Box 89)
  - Food and drink, undated; 2 folders (Box 89)
  - For Kent, undated (Box 89)
  - Frazier's, undated (Box 89)
  - "Get Fresh", undated; 4 folders (Box 89)
  - Hieronymous Seafood Restaurant, undated; 2 folders (Box 89)
  - Homes, home décor, undated; 2 folders (Box 89)
  - Hospitals, medical, undated; 2 folders (Box 89)
  - Housing, undated (Box 89)
  - Insurance, undated (Box 89)
  - Jewelry, undated (Box 89)
  - Kapp's, undated (Box 89)
  - Kiss 102, undated (Box 89)
  - Lawn care, undated (Box 89)
  - Leith Acura, undated (Box 89)
  - Lodging, hotels, resorts, undated (Box 89)
  - Military, undated (Box 89)
  - Mom and dad, don't use drugs PSA, undated (Box 89)
  - Native American remembrance, undated (Box 89)
  - New River Shopping Center, undated (Box 89)
  - News, undated (Box 89)
  - Newspapers and magazines, undated (Box 89)
  - Outdoors, Earth Day, undated (Box 89)
  - Owens PA Center, undated (Box 89)
  - Parks and zoos, undated (Box 90)
  - People, undated (Box 90)
  - Pest control, undated (Box 90)
  - Phone services, undated (Box 90)
  - Public service, patriotic, undated (Box 90)
  - Radio stations, undated; 2 folders (Box 90)